-= CHD字幕组 原创翻译 =-
字幕仅供翻译学习交流 谢绝用于任何商业用途
翻译：dengpao
校对：dxch
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi.  - Hi.
几位？
How many?
两人
Two.
我想要个保险箱 可以吗？
Listen, I wanted to get a safe deposit box. Can you do that for me?
好的 开门营业一小时之后
Okay. Your box will be available
直到关门前30分钟这段时间
any time from an hour after opening
您随时可以使用保险箱 这是钥匙
to 30 minutes before close. This is your key.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果你顺带开活期账户的话
Oh, um, also, if you open a checking account,
保险箱给你5%优惠 还赠送免费透支保护
we'll give you 5% off the box along with free overdraft protection.
其实我更想要一个免费烤面包机
Oh, here I was hopin' for a free toaster.
银行怎么可能送免费烤面包机？
Why would a bank give out free toasters?
喂 小马
Hello, Ma.
我替你点了法式吐司
I'm ordering you the French toast.
不要 谢谢
No, thank you.
我们的女招待麦琪非常有耐心
Our very patient waitress, Maggie,
她胸牌上写着麦琪
well, at least it says Maggie on her name tag,
已经第四次问我要不要点单
has asked me to order four times.
如果我这次还不点 那就太粗鲁了
If I don't order at this point, it's just rude.
- 我还是等下再来  - 不必
- I can come back.  - No, it's okay.
知道吗？ 我已做出最终决策
You know what? I'm making an executive decision.
- 煎饼  - 好的
- Pancakes.  - Okay.
不要煎饼 我不喜欢煎饼 不要煎饼
No pancakes. I don't like pancakes. No pancakes.
你共产党啊？
What are you, a communist?
我朋友点煎饼和煎蛋
My friend'll have the pancakes and a fried egg.
我来份碎肉 但是肉不要太碎 好吗？
I'm thinkin' hash, but only if it's like chunky style, okay?
听着 如果要我吃煎饼和煎蛋 我就踢你屁股
Listen, if you order me eggs and pancakes, I'm gonna kick your behind.
但你应该吃早饭 一日之计在于晨嘛
But you gotta eat breakfast. It's the most important meal of the day.
女士 别听他瞎掰 好吗？
Uh, ma'am, ignore everything he said, okay?
别给我煎饼和煎蛋
Don't bring me any eggs and pancakes.
给我咖啡 煎蛋给他就行
Just bring me some coffee and bring him a couple eggs.
我不要鸡蛋 碎肉饼就可以
I don't want eggs. I want hash.
这样吧 窝俩鸡蛋在上面
You know what, put a couple eggs on it.
给他一份黑麦吐司
Give him some rye toast, too.
别给我黑麦吐司 我不喜欢黑麦吐司
No rye toast for me. I don't like rye toast.
- 那就来煎饼  - 不要煎饼
- And a pancake.  - No pancakes.
要么来份迷你的 你们有迷你煎饼吗？
Maybe a little silver-dollar one. You got the little baby ones?
不要煎饼 也不要迷你煎饼 不要黑麦吐司 我喜欢粗面包
No pancakes, no silver dollars, no rye toast. I like pumpernickel.
我们有粗面包 就粗面包吐司
I do have pumpernickel. Pumpernickel toast.
- 麦琪 等下 还有  - 好的
- Hey, Maggie, wait. One more thing.  - Yeah.
这给你 你带着直到我们再遇见
That's for you. You take that with you till we see each other again
免得你太过于想我 好吗？
in case you miss me too much, okay?
- 你为什么那么做？  - 做什么？
- Why you gotta do that?  - What?
向女招待那样眨眼？
Wink at the waitresses like that?
女招待喜欢我 没有人喜欢你
- Waitresses like me.  - Nobody likes you.
- 那？  - 那么
- So?  - So.
有啥发现？
What do ya got?
一家死气沉沉的银行
So, it is a sleepy bank.
- 有料么？  - 没错
- Doable?  - That's correct.
我就说过
I told you.
好多甜甜圈
That is a lot of doughnuts.
你的碎肉马上到
I'll be right back with your hash.
麦琪 你家的自制甜甜圈 好吃吗？
Maggie, your hot homemade doughnuts, they any good?
- 横贯别家甜点三条马路  - 我说麦琪
- Best in three counties.  - I'll tell you what you do.
那边有三个家伙我看着很来气
You bring us three of those bad boys.
我们要打包带走 好吗？
Put'em in a to-go box for us, all right?
- 好的  - 谢谢
- All right.  - Thank you.
好的 该走了
All right, time to make the move.
很好 这里一定有警报器
All right, there's gonna be some sirens in this bitch.
我去把它弄响
I'm gonna go shake the weasel.
弄响警报器 去弄响警报器
Shake the weasel. Gonna go shake the weasel.
- 早上好 先生 你好吗？ - 早上好
- Hey. Good morning, sir. How are you?  - Morning.
嘿 麦琪
Hey, Maggie.
替我朋友抱歉
I'm very sorry about my friend.
他小时候脑袋被驴踢了
He was kicked in the head as a child.
- 他没有这么讨厌  - 不 他很讨厌
- He's really not that bad.  - No, he is.
怎么了？
What's goin' on?
好吧 我要你们都离开
Okay, I'm just gonna have you all exit the building.
或许是假警报 但是还是离开比较安全
It might be a false alarm, but just do it safely.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
所有人都出来了吗？ 我要你们都待在外面
Is everybody out? I'm gonna need you to step outside.
好了 麦琪 我要去找我的朋友
All right, Maggie, I'm just gonna grab my friend.
- 好的  - 我们会买单的
- Okay.  - We gotta pay our bill.
我们该走了
We should go.
你就留这么点小费？
Is that all you're gonna leave for a tip?
这是15% 你留下15%的小费
It's 15%. You leave 15%.
不 你至少应该留30%的小费
No, you gotta leave at least 30.
不 不行 标准是15%
No, you don't. 15% is standard.
我的麦琪都快没有工作了 老兄 别这么抠
My Maggie's about to be out of a job, man. Don't be cheap.
好吧 那加5块 7块
Okay, there's five. That's seven.
这边走 快点
There you go. Come on.
好了
All right.
什么？ 你不要这样
What? No, you didn't.
是的 我就这样 我的天啊
- Yes, I did.  - Oh, my God.
古人怎么云的？
How'd you say it?
永远不要打劫一家
Never rob a bank across from the diner
正对一家牛皮哄哄的甜甜圈店的银行
with the best doughnuts in three counties?
就是这句
That's correct.
双 龙 出 手
（一周前）
（墨西哥 索诺拉省）
鲍比 帕皮在马棚
Bobby. Papi's down in the stables.
为什么你不去吃点东西？
Why don't you get somethin' to eat?
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
- 你当然饿了  - 我要和你一起去
- Sure you are.  - I wanna come with you.
听着 我们是来办事的 外交事务
Hey, listen. We're here to do business. Diplomatically.
好啊 我外交是特长
Well, I can be diplomatic.
你也饿了 对吗？
You can be hungry, too, right?
鲍比
Bobby.
- 等在这  - 好吧
- Wait here.  - Okay.
这有人坐吗？
Somebody sittin' here?
小托罗
Little Toro.
来得早不如来得巧啊
Oh, well, you move your feet, you lose your seat, right?
- 已经掉了脑袋了  - 没错
- Lose your head, too.  - That's correct.
那么 小托罗在哪呢？
So, where is Little Toro?
你刚把他丢下面了
Alllí, where you put him.
- 在这下面？  - 下面就是
- Aqui?  - Allí.
我们玩色子吧
Let's play some dominoes.
- 帕皮准备好见他了  - 好的
- Papi's ready.  - Yeah.
帕皮格力高！
Papi Greco!
“人尽皆知”的鲍比
"I-know-a-guy" Bobby.
是我
That's correct.
出手迅猛又坚若磐石的1963年生人
Quick, an ostrich, a tank of ether, a '63 Impala convertible.
是1964年的
Make it a '64.
来到我的地盘
My side of the border.
我还真认识那家伙
I know a guy.
我怎么跟你形容的？ 他从不说“不” 也不说“或许”
What did I tell you? He never says no, never says maybe,
从不说“我看着办”
never says, "I'll see what I can do."
好公牛
Nice bull.
我希望它是一头好种牛
I hope he's a good breeder.
小托罗真丢脸
That's a shame about Little Toro.
朱里奥抓到他拿回扣
Julio caught him skimming.
那不像小托罗的作风
That don't sound like Little Toro.
那是给我的？ 没错
Is that for me? That's correct.
所有人都会中饱私囊 人之本性
Everybody skims a little cream. It's human nature.
但熟人也不可以姑息
Just 'cause it's human don't mean you let it go.
很正的线条 很正的色彩
Nice lines. Good color.
那当然
That's right.
果然有点本事
He knows a guy.
你有什么给我？
What you got for me?
现金
Cash.
现金？
Cash?
应该给我10万美元成交
Supposed to be givin' me 100,000 to deal.
为什么不给我10万美元的可卡因
Why didn't you give me $100,000 worth of cocaine?
可卡因在哪？
Where's the cocaine?
我的客户想要可卡因
My buyer wants cocaine.
那么就让他拿钱去买可卡因吧
So let him buy cocaine.
他只想买可卡因
That's what he's tryin' to do. He's trying to buy cocaine.
我告诉他我有熟人 所以我就来找你了
I told him I knew a guy, therefore I come to you.
你就是我的 熟人 我也这么告诉过他
You the guy I know. That's why I told him.
那把护照拿回去吧
So take back the passports.
自小托罗事件后 我们不再接受任何新客户
After Little Toro, we're not takin' on any new customers.
好吧 无意冒犯 但是我不是新客户
Well, no disrespect, but I ain't no new customer.
我们交易有好一阵子了
You been dealin' with me for a long time.
护照你留着
You keep the passports.
钱也留着
Keep the money, too.
准备好可卡因的时候再给我
When you're ready to give me the product, give me the product.
在这之前…
Till then...
算你欠我的
You owe me.
这不公平 老兄
It's not very sporting, man.
至少让鸡有机会开枪反击
At least give the chickens a chance to shoot back.
老兄 我只是说 如果是我 我不会杀一个没有抵抗力的动物
Hey, man, I'm just sayin'. If I'm gonna kill a defenseless animal,
我尊重它作为烤肉的牺牲
I'm gonna honor its sacrifice by grilling it into some tasty barbecue.
再说就算击中一泡尿距离的鸡
What I'm not gonna do is torture it
也证明不了什么
just to prove I can't hit anything further away than my own pecker.
你的搭档真是一个吵闹的狗啊
- Your cuate's a real junkyard dog.  - Mmm.
你们是在哪里合伙的？
某天晚上我丢给他一根骨头 丫就跟我回家了
嘿 牛仔 最帅的那个
Hey, cowboy. You, the pretty one.
古人云 “你长了一张只有你妈才会喜欢的脸”
You ever hear the expression, "You got a face only a mother can love"?
但那句不适合你 你比恶魔还要丑
That don't apply to you. You are uglier than the devil's asshole itself.
史迪格！
Stig!
你在干什么？
What are you doin'?
老兄 他们在折磨小鸡们
They're torturing chickens, man.
你吃的是什么？
What are you eatin'?
鸡腿
A chicken.
这不一样 好吗？
Come here. It's not the same thing, okay?
看到桌子边的那个袋子了吗？
See that bag over there by the table?
自助餐桌旁边的土豆沙拉边的
Buffet table next to the potato salad.
对 有个保龄球包 干嘛的？
Yeah, the bowling bag. What about it?
小托罗的头在那个包里
Little Tom's head is in that bag.
- 我勒个擦  - 没错
- Bullshit.  - Yeah.
这太乱了 老兄
You know what? That's fucked up, man.
我们走吧
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa. Let's go. Okay? Come on, let's go.
用英语说话 你TMD
Say it in English, you goat fuck.
吞我个鸡巴
Suck my chicken.
那话从你嘴里出来真好笑 肥仔
That's funny comin' from you, fat boy.
从你一生下来你就看不到你老二
You ain't seen your pecker since you were a baby.
就算使劲压你的肚脐
Just 'cause you put your finger in your belly button
有便便流出来 你就觉得那是你的菊花了
and brown shit comes out don't mean it's your asshole.
- 你说什么？  - 看我的 老兄
- What did you say?  - Don't worry about it, man.
现在把鸡们弄出来 然后弄成该死的烤肉
Now dig 'em up and make some damn barbecue.
再见 小鸡
Bye, chica.
你刚才对着他眨眼吗？
Did you just wink at him?
我对他眨眼了 因为现在他是我的婊子了
I did wink at him, 'cause he's my bitch now.
- 射得好  - 谢谢
- That's good shootin'.  - Gracias.
小托罗没对任何人行过不义 老兄
You know, Little Toro never did nothin' to nobody, man.
我们应该偷帕皮在特雷司・克鲁塞斯银行的藏匿物
We should rip off Papi's stash at the Tres Cruces Savings and Loan.
你知道 帕皮的小弟每两周
You know, Papi's guy delivers a briefcase
会把装满钱的箱子放到特雷司・克鲁塞斯银行
full of money to Tres Cruces every two weeks.
这肯定至少有300万
That's gotta add up to, what, like three million at least.
如果帕皮知道是我们抢了特雷司・克鲁塞斯银行
If Papi knew we were even talkin' about rippin' off Tres Cruces,
那将是我们的脑袋被装到包里 挨着土豆沙拉
it would be our heads in that bag next to the potato salad.
不可能 我们俩的脑袋放不下 包太小了
No way. Our two heads would never fit in a bag that small.
好了 老兄 让我们去抢劫银行吧
Come on, man, let's hit the bank.
小托罗曾是你的朋友 也是我的朋友
Little Toro was your friend. He was my friend.
- 所以？ - 你说所以什么意思？
- So?  - What do you mean "so"?
万一是我呢？ 如果是我的头被帕皮锯掉呢？
What if it was me? What if it was my head Papi ran through the saw mill?
- 你不会步他后尘的？ - 不会
- You wouldn't come after him?  - Nope.
- 你不会杀了他？ - 不会
- You wouldn't kill him?  - Nope.
他居然对你这么干 是我的话就杀了他 知道为什么要杀他？
Shit, man, he did that to you, I'd kill him. You know why I'd kill him?
因为你是我的人 这是规则
Because you're my people and there's a code.
第一没有规则
There is no code, first of all.
你想做什么就做什么 自己考虑后果
You do whatever you gotta do, whatever it takes.
第二呢？
And second?
第二 我们不是公民 因为你不是墨西哥人
Right, we're not people 'cause you don't have people.
没错
That's correct.
来墨西哥的目的是什么？
Purpose for your visit to Mexico?
捕猎鹌鹑
Quail hunting.
我蒂巴城的婶婶心脏病发作 所以我们只能赶紧回家
My aunt in Tuba City had a heart attack so we cut our trip short.
蒂巴城？
Tuba City?
挨着奥德萨市
It's near Odessa.
地方不错？
Nice place?
藏污纳垢之处 但是她是我最爱的婶婶
Hellhole, but she's my favorite aunt.
- 不许动 把手举起来  - 该死
- Don't move. Let me see your hands.  - Oh, shit.
- 交代你们的行程  - 律师
- Tell us about your trip.  - Lawyer.
- 有什么大交易  - 律师
- What's the big deal?  - Lawyer.
你去过索诺拉 对吗？
You were down in Sonora, weren't you?
你不会认为杰赛普探员和缉毒署会不认识你和帕皮格力高吧？
You don't think Agent Jessup and the DEA know about you and Papi Greco?
律师 律师
Lawyer. Lawyer.
他们知道你去了他的农场
They know you were at his ranch.
我知道我需要一名律师
I know I need a lawyer.
跟瑞斯探员谈谈帕皮格力高
Tell Agent Rees about Papi Greco.
- 谁？  - 帕皮格力高
- Who?  - Papi Greco.
那是谁？ 墨西哥圣诞老人还是别的什么？
Well, who's that? Some Mexican Santa Claus or something?
得了 史迪格先生
Come on, Mr. Stigman.
我认为你最好是合作
I think it's in your best interest to cooperate.
别再玩弄愚蠢的把戏了 行不行？
You need to stop playin' the stupid card, all right?
好的 女士 你想怎样我配合就是
Well, ma'am, it's my intent to cooperate with whatever you need.
作为美国人 我知道你在尽忠尽责
I mean, as an American, I know you're just doin' your job,
有时我这种无辜的人会被误抓
and sometimes innocent folks like me get caught up in the system.
好比航空公司也不是故意丢掉你行李的 对吗？
It's like the airlines. They don't lose your luggage on purpose, right?
但轮到谁谁倒霉
But everybody takes it so damn personal.
好吧 史迪格先生 你想玩游戏吗？
Come on, Mr. Stigman. So you wanna play games?
你说呢？
Well, what'd you have in mind?
- 你想帮自己吗？  - 是的
- Do you wanna help yourself?  - Yes.
必须当着他的面？
Do I have to do it in front of him?
好吧 我们谈完了 谢谢你 史迪格先生
All right, we're done here. Thank you, Mr. Stigman.
- 你要走了？  - 对
- You gonna leave?  - Oh, yes.
天啊
Oh, my God.
跟她共事你还怎么能集中注意力 老兄？
How do you concentrate workin' with her, man?
趁谈话的功夫 5个探员把你的车锯成两半了
Five border agents are rippin' apart your car as we speak.
他们什么都不会找到
They ain't gonna find anything.
你把可卡因藏哪儿了？
Where'd you hide the cocaine?
- 他们能听到我们说话？  - 不
- Can they hear us?  - No.
- 他们能看到我们？  - 不
- Can they see us?  - No.
好吧
Okay.
没有可卡因
There was no cocaine.
- 你到那里做了笔交易  - 是的
- You had a deal in place.  - Right.
500本护照换可卡因
Five hundred passports in return for cocaine.
没错
Right.
嘿 鲍比
Hey, Bobby.
你好 戴布
How you doin', Deb?
你搭档史迪格是块料子
Good. Man, your boy Stig's a piece of work.
他对你眨眼了 对吗？
He winked at you, didn't he?
你怎么知道
How'd you know?
鲍比没有拿到可卡因
Bobby didn't get the cocaine.
什么？ 发生什么事了？
What? What happened?
帕皮要给我现金 我跟他说不行
Papi offered me cash. I told him no.
我跟他说先拿着护照
I told him to keep the passports,
所以最后他一定会给可卡因
so, eventually, he's gotta come up with the cocaine.
你不是去替换那个谁 小托罗？
What about this guy you said you could flip? Little Toro?
我就快搞定了
I got him. It's real close.
我真弄不明白你
I don't know who you are anymore.
就像…
It's like...
胳膊不听大脑的使唤
It's like you're out on this limb.
因为沉迷于他们的世界太久
And you've been out there way too long.
你什么意思？
And you're sayin' that to say what?
我不想参加自己人的葬礼
I don't like goin' to the funerals of my own men.
那就别来 老大 别来
Well, then don't come, boss. Don't come.
好吗？
Okay?
我花了生命中的三年
I spent the last three years of my life
用我自己的方式慢慢的匍匐靠近
crawlin' through a Mexican sewer
帕皮格力高的组织
tryin' to work my way up the line to get next to Papi Greco.
你不能现在让我退出
You can't take me off this now.
杰赛普 他就快完了
Jessup, he's close.
- 你现在不能让我退出  - 我知道
- You can't take me off this now.  - I know.
现在不行
Not now.
再过两周
Two weeks.
到那时你还不能置换小托罗 我就撤了你
You don't flip Little Toro by then, I'm pullin' ya out.
谈话结束
We're done.
杰赛普知道我们的事？
Think Jessup knows about us?
什么叫“我们”？ 我们已经不在一起了 记得吗？
What "us"? You don't do "us," remember?
我想起来了
Oh, I remember.
另外 我在约会
Besides, I'm dating.
好吧 好吧 你在约会
Oh, right, right. You're dating...
你的虚拟男友 哈维
Your imaginary boyfriend, Harvey.
他不是我的男友 他的名字也不叫哈维
Uh, he's not my boyfriend, and his name's not Harvey.
我喜欢哈维 这名字听起来很好 哈维
I like Harvey. It has a nice ring to it. Harvey.
你没必要再吃醋了 鲍比
You don't get to be jealous anymore, Bobby.
哈维
Harvey.
是你把我甩了
You pushed me away.
所以你就可以跟哈维在一起了
So you could be with Harvey.
去你的
Fuck you.
小托罗死了
Little Toro's dead.
你跟杰赛普说你就快搞定他了
You told Jessup you were close to flipping him.
没错
I was.
但当我到达农场
But when I got down to the ranch,
帕皮的跟班把他的头装在包里
Papi's boys was throwin' his head around in a bag.
这便是游戏规则
Well, that's game, then.
小托罗已死 杰赛普会撤掉你
With Little Toro off the board, Jessup's pulling you out.
只要你不跟他交代
Not if you don't tell him.
- 我是你的控制者 鲍比  - 没错
- I'm your control, Bobby.  - That's correct.
我必须说给他听
I have to tell him.
所以我需要你
That's why I need you
让我去抢劫特雷司・克鲁塞斯银行
to let me rob Tres Cruces Savings and Loan.
你要抢劫银行？
You want to rob a bank?
不 是史迪格想抢银行 他的主意
No, Stig wants to rob the bank. It's his idea.
所以不会有陷阱
So there's no entrapment.
我想要的是…
What I want is access to that money
证明帕皮确实把钱存在保险箱里
that Papi's got in the safe deposit box.
不会有哪个法官会为了保险箱
You know no judge is gonna give you
给你签发搜查令的
a blanket warrant for the boxes.
无需搜查令 即便这是脏钱
We don't need a warrant. Not if the money's evidence in a crime.
我们只是追查它的来龙去脉
We just trace it back to ownership,
我们查到帕皮可能逃税 涉嫌违反反诈骗腐败组织集团犯罪法
we got Papi on tax evasion, possible RICO.
- 是吗？  - 是的
- Yeah?  - Yeah.
那史迪格怎么办？
And what about Stig?
他？
What about him?
他是附属牺牲品
He's a side dish.
你只需在银行外面逮捕他
You bust him in front of the bank,
他就得在监狱里待上20年 而你则获得奖章
he does a smooth 20 years in the penitentiary, you get a medal.
银行事件会让我们抓到帕皮
The bank gets us Papi.
该说的都说了 对吧？
And that's all that matters, right?
无论代价如何 宝贝
It takes whatever it takes, baby.
你真的爱我吗？
Did you ever really love me?
我真的爱你
I really meant to love you.
该死
Shit.
没必要敲门 门总是开着的
You don't have to knock. It's always open.
好 我们去打劫银行吧
Yeah, good. Let's hit the bank.
我们去打劫银行
Let's hit the bank.
- 特雷司・克鲁塞斯银行？  - 没错
- The Tres Cruces?  - That's correct.
该死
Oh, shit.
我还在琢磨怎么离开边境线呢
Here I am still spinnin' about how we got yanked outta line at the border.
那么你加入还是不加入？
So you in or you out?
我加入 好吧 只是…
I'm in, yeah. It's just...
你以前干过吗？
have you ever had anything like that happen to you before?
我是说 他们100%相信我们另有所图
I mean, they were 100% convinced we were holding.
如果帕皮不赖掉那笔可卡因的话 我们会有抓他的证据
And we would've if Papi hadn't welched on that coke.
你话里有话吗？
So you're sayin' that to say what?
我说 你听而已
I'm sayin' it's only 'cause you're hearin' it.
不 你话里有话
No, you sayin' somethin'.
你说的话我都听到了 你必有隐言
And if you sayin' it, I'm hearin' it 'cause you're sayin' it.
说吧 开诚布公
What are you sayin'? Let it be said.
我感觉你在玩我
I think you're fuckin' playin' me.
你喜欢被耍？
Are you wanna be played?
我跟在你屁股后面10个月了
I've been at your hip for 10 months,
上次之后 我认为或许你在耍我
but after this, I think maybe you're playin' me.
- 我吓到你了  - 才没有
- I got you.  - No, you didn't.
我赢了 你的眼角抽动了
Oh, I did. The corner of your eye was twitchin'.
眼角？那不是动
The corner? That wasn't a twitch.
- 是眨眼  - 眨眼是我的招牌动作
- That was a wink.  - That's my move.
帕皮家的小胖子在那儿
Yup, that's Papi's chubby little kid right there.
他妈的真能吃油炸玉米粉饼
Feed that motherfucker quesadillas...
我的天
Oh, my God.
这女人真圆润
She's chubby, too.
前凸后翘啊
In all the right places.
老家伙怎么搞到这货色的？
How does an old, fat, ugly fuck get a girl like that?
有钱嘛
Money.
好了 我们走
All right, here we go.
每两周一次
Same thing every two weeks.
帕皮带着满满一箱子现金穿越边境线
Papi flies over the border with a briefcase full of cash.
和情妇待上一礼拜
He spends a week with the mistress.
雪貂鼻朱里奥开车
Ferret Nose Julio drives it out
把钱存到特雷司・克鲁塞斯银行
to the Tres Cruces Savings and Loan.
你觉得他们在银行至少放了三百万
Think they got three million in the bank, huh?
易如反掌
Easy.
来了
Bingo.
钱 钱 钱 钱
Money, money, money, money.
为什么你不去甜甜圈店搞定晚餐呢？
Why don't you hit the diner and check out the doughnuts?
跟你说实话吧 我更喜欢吃碎牛肉
I'm kinda more in a corned beef hash mood, to tell you the truth.
古人云:
You never heard the saying,
永远不要打劫一家
"Never rob a bank across from a diner
正对一家牛皮哄哄的甜甜圈店的银行
that has the best doughnuts in three counties"?
- 狗屁古人  - 古人就这么说的
- That's not a saying.  - Yes, it is.
- 我懂你意思 但那不是古人云  - 你没听过吗？
- I get what you're sayin', but it's not a saying.  - You never heard it?
马上应验给你看
It is a saying. It's a saying now.
你丫的
Okay. Let you tell it.
行动
Make the move.
死缉毒署探员
Bad DEA agent.
- 我坏不坏？ - 你相当的坏
- Am I bad?  - Yes, you are.
我是一个坏女人么
I'm a bad girl?
没错
Yes, you are.
明天3点 史迪格决定抢劫银行
Stig decided to hit the bank tomorrow, 3:00.
史迪格的决定？
Stig decided?
不管有没有我  他都会去
Well, with or without me, he's goin' in.
我还没跟杰赛普说呢
Well, I still haven't talked to Jessup.
史迪格不知道 明天3点他就要进套了
Stig doesn't know that. 3:00 tomorrow he's goin' in.
如果我们想抓帕皮 我就得跟他一起去
If we want Papi, I gotta go in with him.
你都不给我机会 对吗？
You're not even gonna give me a choice, are you?
你没得选 为了保护你
I'm givin' you no other options as a way to protect you.
3点05分当我们出来的时候 让军队候在银行外面
Just have the troops meet me outside the bank, 3:05 when we come out.
3点05分
3:05.
好吧 别开枪打我
Okay. And don't shoot me.
- 即便你想这么做  - 我们走着瞧
- Even if you want to.  - We'll see.
护照和驾驶证 牛仔
License and registration, cowboy.
很好
Cute.
- 你好 提莫？  - 你好么 老兄？
- What's up, Teemo?  - What's up, brother?
- 你好么 兄弟？ 我想你 老兄 　－　我也想你 老兄
- How are you, brother? I miss you, man.  - I miss you, man.
替你带了特制面包酱的土耳其汉堡
Got you a turkey burger. Special sauce.
指挥官想要见你
Commander wants to see you.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
这里离家大老远吧
So, half a mile from home.
我和鲍比上足发条预备行动 长官
I got Bobby all wound up and ready to go, sir.
你要的武器
Ordnance you requested.
海军上将以你为傲
Do you know, the Admiral's proud of what you've done.
你此行将会孤立无援
You've gone way out on a limb.
如果明天银行的事情完了
If the bank falls right tomorrow,
他说你可以回来重返弟兄身边
he says you can come in from the cold, rejoin your brothers.
好极了 能穿回制服的感觉很好 长官
Great. Be good just to put the uniform back on, sir.
我没有穿海军制服就是为与毒贩打交道
I didn't join the Navy to commit felonies and hang with drug dealers.
即便你更适合做毒贩？
Even if you're damn good at it?
我是为国效忠 长官
I do what I do for the Navy, sir.
这都是海军上将计划的一部分
It's all part of the Admiral's plan.
弄到这银行里免费的300万
We get this three million from the bank,
追查跨境运作的帕皮集团及其它垄断组织
we run cross-border ops on Papi and all the other cartels.
明天务必要干净利落
So tomorrow, clean and precise.
清掉所有的保险箱 不能遗落任何一个 明白吗？
Tick all the boxes, nothing left undone. You got it?
是 长官
Yes, sir.
走
Let's go.
嘿 不错的制服
Hey, nice jacket.
嘿 告诉你妈妈她得…
Hey, tell your mother she's gotta move out
搬出我的房子 老兄
of my house at some point, man.
好了 你选哪个 小丑还是佛兰基？
All right, what do you want, clown or Frankie?
佛兰基
Frankie.
点22的枪你打算干嘛？
So, what'd you do with the 22?
用来跟我我表哥换一个咖啡机
Traded to my cousin for an espresso machine.
那你一定有些好料值得研磨？
You're gonna need special beans for that, right?
你可以摸到枪 但我不保证你能不能还扣得到扳机
You can reach for your firearm, but do it real slow.
大楼里还有别的警察吗？
Any other people in the buildin'?
- 怎么回事？ - 银行抢劫
- What the hell is this?  - It's a bank robbery.
只不过是先抢劫警署
Only instead of robbin' the bank
省得你们追我们
and lettin' you chase after us,
我们决定先搞定你们
we decided to come after you first.
我们走
Let's go.
好了 那边的人把枪给我
All right, give me your gun, there.
所有人坐下 所有人坐在地上
All right, everybody sit down. Everybody sit down on the floor.
柜台后面的女士 让我看到你们的手不要按警报
Ladies behind the counter, keep your hands visible, not on the alarms.
来吧 来吧
Let's go, let's go!
没事的 姑娘们 只要给他们抽屉里的现金就行了
It's all right, girls. Just give 'em the drawer cash.
我们说了要抽屉里的现金了吗？
Did we ask for the drawer cash?
快点 快点 快点 坐在这儿 坐下 坐下
Come on, come on, come on. Sit right here. Sit, sit.
我们走 坐在地板上
Let's go, on the floor.
嘿 门卫！
- Hey, guard!  - Hey! Hey.
我想要保持礼貌 懂吗？
Look, I'm tryin' to be polite, all right?
坐好了 很快就结束
Just sit tight and this'll be over soon.
把门打开
Open the gate.
我没有钥匙
I don't have a key.
你说什么？
What'd you say?
放松
Easy.
你再对我说谎 那他妈就好玩了
You lie to me again, it's gonna be more than a fuckin' problem.
现在离开这
Get out there, now.
待在地板上
Get on the floor.
好了没有？ 我进来了
You good? I'm goin' in.
嘘 没事的
Shh. It's all right.
哦 蒂莫西
Oh, Timothy.
嘿 没事的
Hey, it's okay.
没事的 好吗？
It's okay. Yeah?
好了 给你
Okay. Here you go.
表演时间！ 小心爆炸！
Showtime! Fire in the hole!
我勒个擦！
Holy shit!
嘿 佛兰基 情况不对啊
Hey, Frankie, somethin's not right.
这里面装的都是钱
They're all stuffed with money.
我以为你说是一个或者两个箱子
I thought you said there would only be one or two.
每个箱子都有
Every single one of them.
我数了32个箱子 还没完
I'm at 32 boxes and counting.
卡门 这绝对不止300万
Look, there's way more than 3 million.
这边还有更多
And there's still a lot more here.
好吧 把钱都带上 我们一会儿再仔细找
All right, well, take 'em all. We'll figure it out later.
你先搬 我收拾下摊子
You go ahead, I'll get the rest.
好的
All right.
听着
Listen.
外面或许有枪战 好吗？ 如果打起来
May be gunfire outside, okay? So if it hits,
你带着所有人藏在柜台后面
you get everybody behind the counters.
街的对面就是监狱
This is for the jail across the street.
你把警察放出来 让他们到外面去
You let the cops out. Let'em out.
快点
Come on.
这他妈的远远不止300万
That is a hell of a lot more than $3 million.
你数过了？
How much, you figure?
我们可能是这世界上最幸运的笨蛋了吧？
We couldn't be the luckiest chumps on the face of the earth, could we?
- 你觉得幸运？  - 不觉得
- You feel lucky?  - No, I don't.
我是说 这不能是帕皮的钱
I mean, this can't be Papi's money.
因为这些钱警察会追我们到天涯海角的
People are gonna chase us off the end of the earth for money like this.
我不想告诉你这些 史迪格 但是我还有更坏的消息
Well, I hate to tell you this, Stig, but I got more bad news...
你现在慢慢地把手拿开 鲍比
You take that hand away nice and slow, Bobby.
好的
Okay.
把枪放下 史迪格
Put the gun down, Stig.
你知道我真的喜欢你的 对吗？
You know I really like you, right?
我也喜欢你
I like you, too.
- 不 你不喜欢  - 不 我喜欢
- No, you don't.  - Yes, I do.
没有人喜欢我 好吗？ 我习惯了
Nobody likes me, okay? And I'm okay with it.
我喜欢 我比大部分人都喜欢
I do. I like you more than most.
要不是我拿枪指着你 你才不会那么说
You're not just sayin' it 'cause I got a gun pointed to you?
为什么你不把枪先放下？
Why don't you just put the gun down?
该死
Shit.
打得好！
Hot-doggin'!
对不起 老兄
I'm sorry, man.
你为什么那么做？
What'd you do that for?
- 该死 老兄 我不得不这么做！ - 不 你不能
- Shit, man, I had to!  - No, you didn't.
只是一点皮肉伤 你会没事的
It's just a little flesh wound. You'll be all right.
喝点水 然后你就能…
Drink the water, and then you'll be able...
那是什么？
What is that?
你手里拿着的 是警徽吗？
In your hand. Is that a badge in your hand?
告诉我你不是卧底 狗娘养的
Tell me you're not a no-good, two-timin' son of a bitch.
双重卧底？
Two-timin'?
- 不如你告诉我  - 开枪打我啊
- Tell me.  - You shot me.
缉毒署
等一下 等一下 伙计
Hey, wait a minute. Wait a minute, man. Hang on.
不 你等去吧
No, you wait a minute.
史迪格
Stig.
美国是世界上最伟大的国家
The United States is the greatest country in the world
因为我们从内心接受每一种人
because we accept a man is, at his core,
贪婪的人
greedy,
自私的人
selfish
还有贪心的人
and covetous.
我别无选择 他们拿走了我的钥匙
I had no choice. They took my key.
我绝不愿意打开保险库
I would never willingly open the vault.
请把你的手放在桌子上
Keep your hands on the desk, please.
在美国 所有人都得排队
In America, we line everybody up.
说 “要靠自己
Say, "You're on your own."
抓住一切机遇”
"Grab all you can grab."
我是无辜的
I'm innocent.
没有人是无辜的 朋友
Nobody's innocent, friend.
唯有有罪的
There's just the guilty,
无知的
the ignorant
和倒霉的
and the unlucky.
是你拿了我们的钱？
Did you take our money?
你们看起来像在等公交车
You fellas look like you're waitin' for a bus.
你早晚要完蛋
You guys let us know when you're done.
我完蛋了 感谢你的仁慈
Oh, I'm done, and thank you for the courtesy.
那家伙是谁？
Who is that guy?
你听说过上帝暗地里留了一手吗？
You heard of the hidden hand of God?
那就是上帝狗娘养的私生子
Well, that's God's son of a bitch.
打电话给DDO 列出知道我们有存款在这里的人名单
Call the DDO and get a list of everyone who knew we had money in this bank.
你们两个戴着墨镜看起来十足蠢蛋
You two realize those sunglasses make you look like assholes.
请问 那个饭店什么时候被烧的？
Excuse me, when'd that diner burn?
昨天
Yesterday.
我想见一下服务生
I want interviews with the wait staff
以及那家所有的顾客
and every customer in the place.
精制油意外燃烧引发的火灾
It was just a grease fire.
我问你的意见了吗 格莫 ？
Did I ask your opinion, Gomer?
古人云
You ever hear the saying,
“永远不要打劫一家
"Never rob a bank across from a diner
正对一家牛皮哄哄的甜甜圈店的银行”？
with the best doughnuts in three counties"?
如果那家店的火灾是偶然的
If that diner fire's a coincidence,
绝对是因为我们查得还不够仔细
it's only 'cause we ain't looking hard enough.
这么多钱真令人印象深刻啊
That is an impressive amount of greenbacks.
一共是4312.5万 长官
43,125,000 of 'em, sir.
再点一遍 把它们收起来 搬到证物间去
Recount it. Pack it up. We'll stow it back in Corpus.
令我惊奇的是 我们原本是最多
It was my impression we were supposed to come out of that bank
带着300万出来的 长官
with 3 million at most, sir.
这是谁的钱？
Whose money was it?
坏人不值得拥有它们
Bad men unworthy of it.
你知道鲍比・比恩斯是缉毒署的吗？
Did you know Bobby Beans was DEA?
不知道
No, I didn't.
无意冒犯 长官 但是你还没有学会控制表情不外露
No offense, sir, but you really need to work on your surprised face.
如果他是缉毒署的 等于他帮我打劫了银行
Well, if he was DEA, he helped you rob a bank.
意思是他也不干净 于此无需仁慈
Which means he's dirty, and for that, I have no mercy.
- 你把他扔到哪了？ - 沙漠里
- Where'd you leave him?  - In the desert.
- 他死了吗？  - 很可能
- Is he dead?  - More than likely.
“很可能”
"More than likely."
你跟我解释一下那什么意思？
You wanna tell me what that means?
计划的重点是设计鲍比・比恩斯
The whole point of you working with Bobby Beans
令其自杀 造成掮客的假象
was to kill him off and create a cut-out
然后犯罪组织就不会追查到我们
so the OP couldn't get traced back to us.
我无懈可击 他们没办法查到
My cover's solid. There's no way it'll trace back.
我无懈可击 他们没办法查到 长官
My cover is solid. There's no way it'll trace back, sir.
你过于高估你的薪水等级了
That's a call made above your pay grade.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
派两个人把钱送到海军基地
Assign two of the boys to stow the money back at the naval base.
剩下的人跟我一起去检查比恩斯的尸体
The rest'll come with us to check on the body of Mr. Beans.
史迪格 要和我一起吗？
Stigman, wanna come with me?
嘿 老兄
- Hey there, buddy.  - Hey.
你是哈勃？
You habla?
是的 是的
Yeah, yeah.
我是哈勃
I hablo.
好的 那很好
Good, that's good.
别相信他 除非看到证件
Don't trust in him till you see his paper.
如果他有证件 我会看到 你有证件吧？
If he's got papers, I'll see his papers. You got papers, right?
没 没 我没有证件
No. No, I got no papers.
那就成问题了
Well, that's gonna be a problem.
瞧 史利姆杰和我把自己安排到这里
See, Slim Jay and me, we done assigned ourselves
是为了保护这里的边境
protection this here stretch of the border.
官方或者非官方的
Officially unofficially.
我们必须看你的证件
So we really gonna have to see your papers.
确定你不是穆斯林或者别的什么
Make sure you ain't no Muslim or nothin'.
好吧 好 我确实有
Oh, yeah. No, I do have it.
把你的枪给我
And let me have your gun.
把它给我
Give it to me.
谢谢
Gracias.
知道怎么祈祷吗？
You know how to pray?
提莫 现在怎么办 伙计们？
Teemo. How we doin', boys?
有鲍比・比恩斯的任何迹象吗？
Any sign of Bobby Beans?
检查东南方的滩涂
Checked all the washes to the southeast.
没有尸体的痕迹
No sign of a body.
好吧
All right.
好吧 史迪格 你给我们挖了个坑
Well, Stig, you put us in quite a hole.
我不那样看 长官 但是你挂着遮羞布
I don't see it that way, sir, but you're the man with the oak leaves.
我以你为骄傲的理由
All that pride I had in you.
是因为忠诚？
That loyalty?
你刚把它丢弃在风中
You just tossed it to the wind
是的 长官 对不起 长官
Yes, sir. I'm sorry, sir.
该死的
God damn it.
他在峡谷！
He's in the wash!
快 快 快！
Go, go, go!
快点 我们把他赶出来！
Come on, let's flush him out!
你要去哪儿 史迪格 ？
Where you going, Stigman?
你跑也没用的
It doesn't matter if you run.
你的制服没了 你行刺宪兵后的六个月里擅离职守
Your jacket's wired, so you're six-months AWOL after stabbing an MP.
即便你跟别人说 他们也会
You talk to anyone, they're just gonna
把你移交给我的
hand you right back over to me.
你没事吧？
You all right?
- 是的  - 那就TMD的起来！
- Yeah.  - Then get your ass up!
扔掉枪
Toss the gun.
操！
Fuck!
快！
Move!
快点 快点！
Come on, come on!
该死的！
Damn it!
天啊！叫我怎么办？
Jesus! What am I supposed to do with this?
啊 老兄 啊！
Aw, man. Aw!
拜托
Come on.
我是兽医 不是外科医生
I'm a vet, not a trauma surgeon.
我可帮不了你 你得走了
I can't help you with this, man. You gotta go.
去哪儿？
Go where?
你该走了 我什么也帮不了
You gotta leave. I can't do anything.
坎尼 你记得几个月前
Kenny, you remember a couple of months ago
你要卖给我500支的克他命(一种麻醉剂)？
you offered to sell me 500 hits of ketamine?
是啊 你说你不感兴趣
Yeah, you said you weren't interested.
没错
Right.
因为我是缉毒署探员
'Cause I'm a DEA agent.
如果你不给我处理伤口
And if you don't fix me up,
我就去缉毒署举证你
I'm gonna go to the D.A.,
我要告诉他们 你在多莉・艾莫丝音乐会外面
I'm gonna tell them that you like cruising Tori Amos concerts,
给那些大学女孩卖K粉
selling Special K to little weepy college girls.
你不可能是警察的
There's no way you're a cop.
- 不可能？ -不
- No?  - No.
- 你确定？ - 我确定
- You sure?  - I'm positive.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
在法庭上你有权利请律师
You have the right to have a lawyer present during questioning.
还要继续吗？
Do I need to keep going?
不 我很好 你确是警察
No, I'm good. You're a cop.
好的
Okay. Okay.
衬衫不错
Nice shirt.
谢谢 是杰西潘尼牌的
Thanks. It's JCPenney's.
- 是吗？ - 是的
- Yeah?  - Yeah.
好吧 再等一下
All right, hold on one second.
欢迎光临皇家卡米诺
Welcome to the Camino Real.
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊 你来晚了
- You were late.  - Jesus Christ.
到底发生什么了？
What the hell happened?
- 借过一下  - 借过
- Excuse us.  - Excuse me.
我打劫了一家银行 你怎么回事？
I robbed a bank. What happened to you?
3点05的时候我和六个探员在那儿
I was there with six agents at 3:05.
- 不 你没有  - 我去了
- No, you weren't.  - Yes, I was.
你晚了
You were late.
你出来早了
You went early.
本来你拿出你的徽章
And it's not as if you couldn't have
早就可以了结此事
pulled your badge at any time and stopped it.
- 我拿出来了 史迪格开枪打我  - 什么？
- I did. Stig shot me.  - What?
他打中我的肩膀
He shot me in the shoulder.
我们得送你去医院
We gotta take you to the hospital.
打扰你和哈维的约会了？我不想这样
And interrupt your rendezvous with Harvey? I don't think so.
我们要做的是
This is what we need to do,
找到史迪格 找到那些钱
we need to find Stig, we need to find the money.
好吧 听着
All right. Listen.
我上楼找个借口
Let me go upstairs, make my excuses,
然后一起去找史迪格 好吗？
and then we'll find Stig together, okay?
好吧 我们应该这么做
Okay, let's do this. Let's do this.
你先上楼重新检查史迪格的背景资料？
Why don't you recheck Stig's background?
或许我们错过了什么 是吗？
Maybe there was something that we missed. All right?
我去史迪格公寓看有没有其他线索
I'm going to Stig's apartment and see what I can find out.
- 好吗？ - 好
- All right?  - Okay.
代我向哈维问好
Tell Harvey I said hi.
你给谁做过救治了？
Who'd you patch up?
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
我在说什么？
What am I talkin' about?
后院停着一辆沙丘车
Well, there's a dune buggy parked out back
属于一个有枪伤的人抢来的
that was stolen by a man with a bullet hole in him.
在他挨枪子之前
Now, before he had a bullet hole in him,
他烧了一家甜甜圈店 还打劫了一家银行
he burned down a diner and robbed a bank.
我不知道这些事情 所以…
I don't know anything about that, so...
好吧
Okay.
好吗？
Okay?
好得很
Fair enough.
我问你
Say, let me ask you somethin'.
玩过俄式轮盘吗？
You ever play Russian roulette?
当然没有 我想啥呢？
'Course not. What am I thinkin'?
问题是一般人
The thing is, most people,
会把枪指向太阳穴
they put the gun to the temple.
那样太蠢了
And that's, well, that's just stupid.
万一…
What if...
万一子弹在第一发位置呢？
The bullet's in the first chamber?
会直接轰掉脑袋的
You blow a man's head off 'fore he's had a chance
万一他倒是真的有料却不肯告诉你的话
to tell you what you want to know.
不要 不 不 拜托
No. No, no. Come on, man.
真是好运
Case in point.
史迪格！
Stig!
史迪格
Stig.
接电话 鲍比
Pick up, Bobby.
你TMD来这干嘛 鲍比？
What the fuck are you doing here, Bobby?
你在找什么 老兄？
What're you duckin' for, man?
你知道我陷害了你吧？
You know I set you up, right?
他们跟我说了你的一切
They told me all about you.
淘气猫 谁的资料他都有 没亲人
Tough cat. Knows everybody. Doesn't have people.
-那家伙？那家伙是个很好掮客
That guy? Well, shit, that guy's a perfect cut-out.
他吃了一枪 但有谁会在乎呢 对吗？
I mean, he takes a bullet, who's gonna care, right?
接电话
Pick up the phone.
TMD接电话 鲍比
Pick up the damn phone, Bobby.
你有什么要说的？
You got anything to say?
第一个问题
First question,
如果你是缉毒署的 如果你是清白的 为什么独自上阵？
if you're DEA and you're clean, why are you here alone?
你的支援呢 鲍比？
Where's your backup, Bobby?
快点 就是你这种态度
Come on, it's this kind of attitude
让我觉得你不是一个好人
makes me think you're not one of the good guys.
如果我要杀你 在进楼之前
If I wanted you, I could've had you
就能杀你 鲍比
before you walked into that building, Bobby.
那枪不错 史迪格
That's a beautiful rifle, Stig.
是军备用品吧？
Is that Army issue?
你喜欢吗？ 不是军备 是凯马特超市的蓝色特惠货品
You like that? No, it's Kmart. Blue Light Special.
现在回答我的问题 你的支援在哪？
Now answer my question. Where's your backup?
不 不 那是部队装备
No, no, that's a military rifle.
为什么部队的走狗要去打劫银行 史迪格？
What's the military doing robbing banks, Stig?
我们能直话直说吗 鲍比？
Can we just have a straight-up conversation, Bobby?
我分分钟就可以送你去西天
I got you dead to rights.
是吗？ 那么开枪
Yeah? So shoot me.
再打一次
Again.
不敢？
No?
我自己打我自己
I'll shoot myself.
嗯 不错
Huh. Not bad.
我很高兴你印象深刻
I'm glad you're impressed.
你在试我 看会不会先开枪？
Were you testing me to see if I would shoot first?
钱在哪里 史迪格？
Where's the money, Stig?
如果你清白我自然会告诉你 可惜你不是 所以不会告诉你
If I thought you were clean, I might tell you, but I don't, so I can't.
说谎吧你 因为钱不在你那里 钱在哪儿？
You're lying. You don't have it, do you? Where's the money?
- 该死  - 怎么了？
- Oh, shit.  - What?
看来今晚要找我的不止是你
You're not the only one I was expecting.
来了三个淘气包
Three very nasty men just showed up.
如果他们发现你在我的住处 会生气的
If they find you in my place, they will get ugly.
他们是谁？
Who are they?
昨天我说过他们是我的家人
Yesterday I'd have said they were my family.
他们今天就要杀了我
Today they kinda wanna kill me.
- 我了解这种感受  - 你懂个屁
- I understand the feeling.  - You know, fuck you.
你对家人了解多少？你都没有亲人
What do you know about family? You don't even have people.
不 鲍比 那是个坏想法
No, Bobby, that's a stupid idea.
他们已经上楼了
They're already comin' up the stairs.
鲍比！
Bobby!
告诉过你 现在 鲍比
I told you. Now, Bobby,
挂掉免提 打开你的手机
hang up the speaker and answer your cell phone, okay?
如果你想要我帮你脱离…
If you want me to help you out...
呆在阴影里
Just stay in the shadows, okay?
我会指引你出去
I'm gonna guide you out from there.
等着
Wait.
他从你后面过去了 你最好闪过门厅
He's comin' up your rear. You better dart across the hall.
藏到卧室里的储物柜后面
Go over to the bedroom and hide behind the lockers.
去
Go.
行了 鲍比 你最好闪过门厅 快
All right, Bobby, you're gonna wanna scoot across the hall. Go.
鲍比 鲍…
Bobby, Bob...
干
Shit.
- 提莫！- 屋顶！
- Teemo!  - Rooftop!
目标移动中！
Target's on the move!
对不起 提莫
Sorry, Teemo.
钱在哪儿？
Where's our money?
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talkin' about.
你以为缉毒署能轻松的进入我们的银行
You think DEA can just waltz into our bank,
偷走我们的钱 我们却毫不在乎吗？
steal our money, and we're not gonna kick?
你的人鲍比偷了我们4300万美元
Your man Bobby Trench stole 43 million of our dollars.
我们想要回来
We'd like it back.
因为那是我们的钱
Because it's our money.
还因为这是明目张胆的不把我放在眼里
Because it's a blatant act of disrespect.
总之这是我们的钱
And because it's our money.
必须是你打来的 鲍比
Please tell me it's you, Bobby.
关于史迪格有什么新消息吗？
Anything new on Stig?
他马上就会查到我已经删除的数据
He's comin' up clean on every database I'm cleared for.
有没有军方关系或者服役记录？
No military connection? No record of service?
多深入一些 我要杰赛普证明我的清白
To go deeper, I'd need to get clearance from Jessup.
好了 试下你在部队里的老熟人
Well, try your old contacts in the military.
我会告诉杰赛普我知道的所有事
I'm gonna tell Jessup everything I know.
等下 你确定吗？
Wait, are you sure?
有人想知道银行里的钱是谁的
Someone has to know whose money was in the bank.
那人是史迪格
Yeah. Stig.
史迪格甚至还不知道我是美国缉毒署的
Stig didn't even know I was DEA.
更何况 还有人也想杀了他
Besides, somebody tried to kill him, too.
鲍比 让我帮你 还需要什么？
Bobby, let me help you. What do you need?
放松点 拜
Take it easy. Bye.
鲍比
Bobby.
该死！
Fuck!
连一个人都打不过 去把门关上
That's how you take down a man. Now shut the door.
安心去吧
Just let it come.
探员罗伯特 林恩 特伦奇
Agent Robert Lynn Trench.
又称鲍比・T或者鲍比・B 同时也是鲍比比恩斯
A.k.a. Bobby T, a.k.a. Bobby B, a.k.a. Bobby Beans.
我们谈谈吧
Let's have a chat.
你偷了4312.5万元
You stole $43.125 million
不属于你的钱
that did not belong to you.
现在 我们坦率一些
Now, man-to-man,
缉毒署里的谁指使你去抢我们银行的？
who at DEA authorized you to rob our bank?
你是银行家吗？
You a banker?
你有玩过俄式轮盘吗？
You ever play Russian roulette?
问题是
Thing is,
大多数人把枪指着太阳穴
most people put the gun to the temple.
这是很愚蠢的
Well, that's just stupid.
不给他一个机会告诉你想知道的所有事
You blow a man's head off 'fore he's had a chance
就打爆他的头
to tell you what you wanna know.
会弄脏你的外套
Mess up your suit, too.
谁告诉你可以拿走我们的钱？
Who told you it was all right to take our money?
“我们的钱 我们的银行”
"Our money. Our bank."
你是谁？
Who are ya?
如果你连我是谁都不知道
If you don't know who I am,
又怎么知道我们有4300万？
how did you know to steal our 43 million?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
－ 不知道？ - 是的
- You don't?  - No.
好吧…
Well...
钱在哪儿？
Where's the money?
我的乖乖
Oh, boy.
至少不在脚下 我可以向你保证这一点
it ain't down there, I can guarantee you that.
这可是鲍比蛋蛋
A.k.a. Bobby Balls.
剃干净毛的
Clean and shaven.
知道你是什么人吗？
You know what you are?
你
You
是一个黑特工
are a dirty DEA agent.
没错
That's right.
你是一个抢劫银行的黑特工
You're a dirty DEA agent who robbed a bank.
并且杀了你的上司
And shot your boss.
这事情将会在…
You walk into any federal office,
每一间联邦办公室广为人知
and that's the story they're gonna have.
除非你把4312.5万还回来
Unless you bring me $43.125 million,
你就可以清白的走人
and you walk away. Clean.
我打动你了吗？
Have I properly incentivized you?
深深地打动了
More than you know.
不想进监狱的话就快点做吧
Unless you wanna rot in jail, you best get after it.
去吧 现在就去
Go on, now. Go on.
好吧
All right.
你觉得他应该有更好的下场？
You're thinkin' he deserved better?
你说对了
You're right.
嘿 鲁迪
Hey, Rudy.
早上好 贾伟
Hola, Javier.
早上好 帕皮
Morning, Papi.
别动
Don't move.
进房子 快点
Go inside, quick.
妈咪！
Mommy!
我们偷了谁的钱？
Whose money did we steal?
你真的想知道？
You really wanna know?
我真的想知道
I really wanna know.
放松 老家伙 进去 进去
Easy, old man, get in there. Get in there.
你要遭报应
Payback's a bitch!
你要遭报应！
- 哇哦 鲍比  - 放下枪 把钥匙给我
- Whoa, Bobby.  - Drop the gun. Give me the keys.
慢慢地把钥匙给我
Give me the keys. Nice and easy.
我做不到
I can't do that.
- 为什么？  - 我先到场的 我有优先权
- Why not?  - Well, I got him first. I got dibs.
我比你早到44秒 我正在抓帕皮 给我钥匙
I got a .44. I'm taking Papi. Give me the keys.
你想要？ 来拿吧
You want 'em? Come get 'em.
我看到转盘在动
Now, I see the wheels turnin'.
你在想蒙住眼睛 或许用牙齿拿到钥匙
You're thinkin' a little blindfold, maybe use your teeth.
我没这样想 你知道我怎么想的？
That's not what I'm thinkin'. You know what I'm thinkin'?
该死的 老兄 这招怎么样？
Oh, shit, man. How's that?
多此一举
That was uncalled for.
操 我还是喜欢当年的那个小鲍比
Shit. I liked you better when you were "I-know-a-guy" Bobby.
那个鲍比是个好家伙
That Bobby was a good guy.
是的 我喜欢以前那个对着服务生眨眼
Well, I liked you better when you were winkin' at waitresses
并打爆鸡头的你
and shootin' the heads off of chickens.
把钥匙给我 把钥匙给我
Give me the keys. Give me the keys.
- 该死！ - 发生什么了？
Shit!
你看到了吗？没错 给我钥匙
- You saw that move comin'?  - That's correct. Give me the keys.
你真是
Damn, you're good.
现在 我们中的一个要捡起这些钥匙
Now, one of us is gonna have to pick up those keys.
- 猜一下  - 是我会捡起来的 行吧？
- Guess.  - All right. I'll get 'em, all right?
- 捡起来  - 把枪指着其他地方 伙计
- Get 'em, get 'em.  - Put that musket away, man.
- 嘿 停下来！ - 停下来？
- Hey, pull over!  - Pull over?
嘿 帕皮 你喜欢坐我的车吗？
Hey, Papi, you like my drivin'?
糟糕！
Oh, shit!
别这样 鲍比 我不会和你闹一整天的！
Come on, Bobby, I ain't got all damn day!
你想做什么？
What do you wanna do?
好了 没事了 好了 让我走
All right. All right, all right. All right, let me go.
你先放开我
You let me go first.
不 你放开我
No, you let me go.
数到三
On three. On three.
一 二 三
One. Two. Three.
看到了吗？ 现在你让我不能相信你了
See? Now you're making me not be able to trust you.
数到三 我们一起松手
On the count of three, we'll let each other go.
- 好吗？ - 好的 很公平
- All right?  - All right. That's fair.
一 二
One. Two.
三
Three.
我就知道 放开我
I knew it. Let me go.
- 不！ - 我会松手的 我会松手的
- No!  - I'm gonna let you go. I'm gonna let you go.
- 好了  - 一…
- All right.  - One...
好吧 伙计 你必须承认这挺有趣的吧？
Come on, man. You gotta admit, that was kind of fun, no?
你不喜欢？
You didn't like that?
你是谁？
Who are you?
糟糕
Shit.
美国海军情报人员 是吗？
- U.S. Navy Intel.  - Yeah?
或者说曾经是
Or I was.
我的长官因为自己犯错而导致我被取消职位
My commander FUBARed my jacket.
在我刺伤了宪兵后我擅离职守
And now I'm AWOL after stabbing an MP.
你算幸运的 我的罪名是谋杀自己的长官
You're lucky. They got me framed for killing my boss.
你的长官有让你最亲密的四个朋友来杀你吗？
Did your boss order your four closest friends to kill you?
没有 你赢了
No, you got me there.
海军士官迈克尔・史迪格
Petty Officer Michael Stigman.
禁毒官员鲍比・特伦奇 不过我觉得你已经认识我了
DEA Officer Bobby Trench, but I guess you know that already.
幸会
Pleasure.
你对我是歪打正着呢
So, what, you just happened to pick me,
还是受令来陷害我的？
or you got orders to set me up on purpose?
我受令的 但我不知道你是缉毒署的人
I had orders, man. I didn't know you were DEA.
我的人知道 他们有参考消息
My people did. But they're Intel.
他们没什么不知道的
There's not much they don't know.
你的人？
Your people?
现在我得把凌乱的线索拼凑出完整的故事
Now I'm just trying to piece together the truth,
因为我会越级直接去向海军上将汇报
so I can take it over my commander's head to the Admiral.
所以他们想要杀我 并解释我为什么想和帕皮谈话
That's why they wanna kill me and why I wanted to talk to Papi.
明白了
Right.
所以…
Well...
我想我们可以同时跟他对话
I guess we can both talk to him at the same time.
什么 就像搭档一样吗？
What, like we're workin' together?
不 这不意味着我们在合作
No, not like we're working together.
只是表示我们住的比较近而已
- Yeah.  - No, like we're workin' in the same vicinity.
搭档 我们只不过电话区号相同
- Together.  - In the same area code.
搭档 同住一个国家
- Together.  - The same county.
更不要说同住地球村了
And don't get all "We Are The World" on me either.
- 当这件事结束后我还是会射死你  - 但我们是搭档
- When this is over, I'm still gonna shoot you.  - But we're partners.
别这样 伙计 别井水不犯河水的
Come on, man, Ebony and Ivory.
该死 我想他吐了 不是吐了 就是死了
Shit, I think he puked. He's puked or he's dead.
哦 是的 他吐了
Oh, yeah, he puked.
我TMD一定要杀了你们两个
I'm gonna fuckin' kill you both.
这事情有点难度
This might take a while.
我有一整天的时间 伙计
I got all day, partner.
你闻闻看
Hold on.
使劲闻闻看
Let me put that in there with ya. Put that on ya.
搭档 你准备怎么做？
- So...  - Partner, how you wanna do this?
我喜欢你顺其自然的流露
I like that, it's got a nice roll off your tongue there.
我们还没那么亲密 别跟我套近乎 别套近乎
We're not that close. Don't kumbaya with me. Don't kumbaya.
我准备拿上毛巾水桶和冲浪板塞进他的屁股
I'm gonna get my bucket and towel and waterboard his ass.
不 我们要给他一个说话的机会 你有什么想说的吗？
No, we gotta give him a chance to talk. You got anything to say?
我希望你们能喜欢蛋蛋的味道
I hope you guys like the taste of balls,
因为我准备剁下它们再塞进你们的嘴巴里
because I'm gonna chop yours off, stuff 'em in your mouths.
看到吗？
See?
我也可以把你的塞进他嘴巴 把他的塞进你的嘴巴
Or maybe I'll put yours in his and his in yours.
想让我拿桶子来吗？
Want me to get the bucket?
来吧
Kumbaya.
你为什么要把那么多钱放在特雷司・克鲁塞斯？
So why were you puttin' so much money in Tres Cruces?
特雷司・克鲁塞斯银行
It's Tres Cruces.
我们以为你就存放了一点小钱在那儿
We thought you just stashed a little cash there
直到我们抢完银行才发现有4300万美元 为什么？
until we robbed the place, found 40 million. Why is that?
你们抢了特雷司・克鲁塞斯银行？
You robbed Tres Cruces?
没错 为什么？
That's correct. Why is that?
很好笑吗？
That's funny, huh?
你死定了
You're dead.
- 是的 很好笑  - 你们都死定了
- Yeah, that is funny, isn't it?  - You're both dead.
我都不需要亲自动手
And I didn't even have to kill you.
我知道你很厉害 “人尽皆知”的鲍比
I thought you were sharp. "I-know-a-guy" Bobby.
但你…
But you...
刚抢劫了中情局
You just ripped off the CIA.
中情局？
The CIA?
中情局
The CIA.
胡扯 为什么把中情局的钱放在同一家银行？
He's full of crap. Why would he have money in the same bank as the CIA?
你为什么跟中情局在同一家银行里存钱？
Why would you have money in the same bank as the CIA?
那里一毛钱都不属于我
I don't have shit in that bank.
我往特雷司・克鲁塞斯银行存的唯一的钱就是
The only money I deliver to Tres Cruces
给中情局的付款？
- is a payment.  - To the CIA?
中情局拿走我7%的利润
The CIA. They take 7% of my revenue.
作为回报 他们让我用他们的飞机
In return, they let me use their planes
所以我可以带着毒品轻松地飞过边境
so I can get my shit across the border.
我本可以不用花这么多钱 但是根本没得商量
I could do it a lot cheaper, but there was really no negotiations.
你知道…
You know...
他们从每个毒贩手里拿钱
They take it from all the cartels.
放屁
Bullshit.
好吧
Okay.
他们还是会杀了你
They're still gonna kill you.
鲍比？
Bobby?
你说随时都可以收手的
You said stop by anytime.
－ 你绑架了一个毒袅？ - 是的
- You kidnapped a drug kingpin! -That's correct.
帕皮・格力高你还把他绑在车库里！
Papi Greco! And you tied him up in my garage!
不好意思 你要…
不介意我吃罐酸奶吧
You mind if I swipe a yogurt?
得了吧 我把这当做家 想吃什么吃什么
Yeah, sure. Please. Help yourself to anything. Take whatever you want.
只是一杯酸奶而已
It's just a yogurt.
但这是她的酸奶 放回去
But it's her yogurt. Just put it back.
麻烦了
Please.
你们两个以前有过一腿？
Are you two like ex-boyfriend and girlfriend?
其实我们从来都没有正式名分
Actually, you know what? We never put a name on it.
那是你伤了他的心还是他伤了你的？
So, what, you broke his heart or he broke yours?
哇 这个人真是口无遮拦
Wow, this guy will really ask anyone anything at anytime.
你不如去看一下帕皮？
Why don't you go and check on Papi, huh?
你看上了这家伙的哪一点？
What do you see in this guy?
我可以继续好几小时 但我不认识你
I could go on for hours, but I don't know you,
而且我不认为现在的时机适合…
and I don't think this is the right time
聊天 好吗？
for us to have this conversation, okay?
老爸的教诲？
So daddy issues, huh?
老爸的教诲！
Daddy!
去车库 看帕皮去
Garage. Papi. Go.
- 我知道了  - 走 去车库
- I get it now.  - Go. Go to the garage.
- 我能带上这瓶酸奶吗？ - 可以 带上吧
- Can I have the yogurt?  - You can have the yogurt. Here.
我不喜欢她 伙计我不支持你
- I don't like her, man.  - You don't get a vote.
我会盯着她的
I'm gonna watch her.
鲍比 你在做什么？
Bobby. What are you doing?
你确定你能相信这家伙吗？
Are you 100% sure you can trust this guy?
不 但只有他能帮我
No. But he's all the help I got.
杰赛普死了
Jessup's dead.
我们偷的是中情局的钱 他们是来找钱的
The money we stole was CIA money. They came lookin' for it.
对不起德比  我不想让你卷进这件事的
I'm sorry, Deb, I didn't mean to get you involved in all this.
你没事吧？
You okay?
你傻笑什么呢？
What are you smirking at?
我绞尽脑汁的想
You know, I've been racking my brain
想弄清楚你长得像谁
trying to figure out who you look like.
终于想到了
And it finally dawned on me.
你是墨西哥版的爱因斯坦
You look like a Mexican Albert Einstein.
不过明显地 除了他的天才因素
Minus the genius factor, obviously.
想要一些酸奶吗？
You want some yogurt?
报应啊报应
Payback's a bitch.
这一拳为了小托罗
That's for Little Toro.
史迪格
Stig.
史迪格！
Stig!
干掉他！
Pack it up!
快行动 快行动！
Move it, move it!
－ 史迪格 - 就一个人
- Stig.  - The one and only.
那是你的人吗？
That your people?
你一定要这样说吗？
Do you have to say it like that?
难道他们不是你的人吗？
Like what? They're your people, right?
技术上来说是的 但我觉得现在只有你是我的人
Technically, yes, but I thought you were my people now.
好吧 两枪之后 我们上车 准备好
All right, two taps, we'll hit the garage. On go.
- 好了 你准备好就出发  - 走！
- Okay. On your go.  - Go!
该死
Fuck.
那是怎么一回事？
What was that about?
一团糟
That was messed up.
到底怎么了？
What the hell is going on?
毫无头绪
I don't know.
我不知道
把你的手机给我
Give me your phone, now.
车我也要了 下去 下车！
I'll take the car, too. Get out. Get out!
噢 老天
Oh, my God.
我在灰色大道
Está en un gray Charger.
史迪格的人怎么知道你家的？
How did Stig's people know to come to your house?
不知道 他们一定跟踪你们了
I don't know. They must have followed you.
不可能
I don't think so.
我们见过他们
We would have seen 'em.
我们应该见过他们
We should have seen 'em.
他们怎么知道去你家的？
How'd they know to come to your house?
啊？
Hmm?
他们为什么在你家 德比？
Why were they at your house, Debbie?
你认真的吗？
No. You serious?
鲍比
Bobby...
下车
Out of the car, gabacho.
快
Hurry up.
你死定了
You fucked up now, I see.
跪下
On your knees.
我也会喊人的 鲍比
I know some guys, too, Bobby.
绑起来 带回去
Bag 'em up. Let's take 'em home.
- 你想谈一谈吗？ - 不
- Do you wanna talk about it?  - No.
- 确定？ - 确定
- You sure?  - Yeah, I'm sure.
告诉过你我不喜欢她 伙计
I told you I didn't like her, man.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你干嘛要对我生气？
What are you gettin' mad at me for?
因为你叽叽歪歪
Because you talk too much.
我对你做什么了？
What'd I ever do to you?
除了朝我开枪？
Besides shoot me?
你知道你是什么吗？ 你是个愤青
You know what you are? You're a misanthorpe.
是愤青 我是个愤青
It's misanthrope. I'm a misanthrope.
知道我什么意思吗？
Did you know what I meant to say?
不知道 你想说什么？
No. What did you mean to say?
- 你不喜欢人  - 闭嘴
- That you don't like people.  - Shut up.
轮到我按摩了
Time for my massage.
我会叫钟点工帮你换床单的
Yeah. I'll have housekeeping clean up your bed.
该死
Oh, shit.
我爷爷砍了30年的甘蔗 从未起过水泡
My grandfather cut cane for 30 years every day and never got a blister.
据说闻起来很臭
Says it smells like hell,
但双手会很强壮
toughens the hands.
知道我喜欢什么？
You know what I like about this?
不仅是我现在时间够多
Not only do I get to take my time with you guys,
更因为我没有后顾之忧了
but this time, I don't have to worry about leaving any marks.
别用你的手碰我 老家伙
Don't put your hands on me, man.
操！你刚说什么？
- Shit.  - What did you say?
别用你沾了尿的手碰我
Just don't put those pissy hands on me, man.
你无家可归了 鲍比
You ain't got a home, Bobby.
缉毒署不需要你
DEA doesn't want you around.
因为你的罪恶
Not with your sins.
付出报应吧
Payback's a bitch.
你闻起来真臭
You smell like warm Corona, man.
还记得我得过奖的种牛吗
You remember my prize breeding bull.
有着跟椰子一样大的蛋蛋
With cojones the size of coconuts.
想见见它吗？
You wanna see him?
不用了 在这里就看的很清楚
No, it's okay. We can see good from here.
永别了 鲍比
Adiós, Bobby.
不 不
No, no.
我擦！
Shit!
四千三百万！
43 million!
是我们在中情局偷到的所有的钱
It's everything we stole from the CIA.
你让我们走 我们就会带给你
You let us go, we'll bring it to you.
钱在我手上
I got the money.
- 你在说什么？ - 钱在我手上
- What are you talking about?  - I got it.
- 你没有！ - 我知道我没有 但他不知道
- You don't have it!  - I know I don't have it. He doesn't know that.
但你手上没那笔钱
But you don't have the money.
我知道你没有 因为我拿了那些钱
I know you don't have it, 'cause I have it.
你拿了？钱在哪里？
You have it? Well, where is it?
奎恩斯长官的保险箱里
Commander Quince's safe.
天哪 别告诉我 告诉他
- Corpus Christi Naval Air Station.  - Don't tell me. Tell him.
哦 操！
Oh, shit!
在哪里？
Where is it?
奎恩斯长官的保险箱里
Commander Quince's safe! Corpus Christi Naval Air Station!
这家伙在朝我们尿尿 而你还在考虑要不要告诉他
The guy's pissing on us, and you're askin' if we should fuckin' tell him.
真的吗 还是现在杀了你们更好
If that's the truth, I might as well just kill you now.
我手下几个人卧底在你这里
I had a run-in with a couple boys out of your organization.
是谁 厄尔
Hello, Earl.
鲍比・比恩斯先生和迈克尔・史迪格先生
Mr. Bobby Beans and Mr. Michael Stigman.
他们不是我的手下
Well, they're not from my organization.
他们都是外人
They're freelancers.
而鲍比・比恩斯是美国缉毒署的卧底
And Bobby Beans is undercover DEA.
史迪格是美国海军的离职人员
And Mr. Stigman's AWOL U.S. Navy.
他们偷了特雷司・克鲁塞斯4312.5万美元
They stole 43.125 million from the Tres Cruces.
我们想拿回来
We want it back.
有没有酬金？
Is there a finder's fee?
酬金就是允许你继续做生意
Fee is we let you continue to do business.
酬金就是我们不会把我们的提成从7%提升到20%
Fee is we don't raise our cut from 7% to 20.
酬金就是我们不会带着一个中队的阿帕奇A6直升机来这里
The fee is we don't come down here with a squad of Apache A-6 helicopters
把你从地球上抹去
and wipe you off the face of the earth.
你希望我的国家变得虚弱和腐败吧？
You like my country weak and corrupt, don't you?
以便在超市能买到一些便宜货
So you can buy your cheap crap at the mall.
好吧 厄尔 我可不是好欺负的
Well, Earl, I'm not cheap.
这有关你的尊严 曼尼？
Is this about pride, Manny?
男子汉气概？
About machismo?
证明你是个墨西哥大枭？
Prove you got a big Mexican cock?
好吧 你是个大人物 非常牛逼
Well, your cock is huge. It's massive.
而且我非常的敬畏你
And I, I'm in awe of your cock.
那又怎样？ 你还是个毒贩
So what? You're still a drug dealer.
而我还是美国政府官员
And I'm still the government of the United States.
市场是自由的 曼尼
It's a free market, Manny.
但世界并不是自由
Not a free world.
这事我留意一下
I'll take a look.
很难看！你会死的很难看的
Hard! You'll look hard.
翻遍墨西哥的每一块石头
Under every rock in Mexico.
离开这个鬼地方
Let's get out of this shithole.
把后面那俩家伙洗洗干净
如果那白人真的是美国海军 还有可能拿回4300万
中情局的人怎么办？
让他去死
得令 老板
我决定让你们带给我4300万
I've decided to let you bring me the 43 million.
卡车会把你们带到边境
The truck'll take you north to the border.
从那里开始你们要靠双脚
From there, you'll cross on foot with the coyotes.
我宁愿开车过去
If it's all the same, we'd rather drive.
所有人都在找你们
With everybody lookin' for you,
他们马上就会抓住你
they'd pull you out of line in two seconds.
所以不行 你要走我们的人走的路
No, you go the way you force my people.
如果我们过不来
If we can't risk crossing,
怎么把钱给你？
how are we supposed to bring you back the money?
我会在北部边境24小时等你们
I'll meet you north of the border in 24 hours.
我相信你们会履行你们的诺言的
Now, I'm trusting you to fulfill your part of the bargain.
嘿 鲍比
Hey, Bobby.
你有24小时搞钱
You got 24 hours to bring me the money.
不然我打爆她的头
Or I'm gonna shoot her right in the head.
然后找到你
Then I'm gonna find you,
像杀猪一样把你的肠子挖出来
and I'm gonna gut you like a pig!
史迪格！
Stig!
这事完后 我还是会对你开枪
When this is over, I'm still gonna shoot you.
无所谓的 鲍比
Whatever it takes, Bobby.
挑一辆 我都可以搞定
Pick one. I can get in anything.
奥迪怎么样？
So, what about the Audi?
不 德国车我不干 车锁太复杂 太多警报
No, I don't do German, okay? Locks are tricky, too many alarms.
好吧 那萨伯曼？
Okay. Suburban?
那是2010年的款
That one's 2010.
每两英里就要一加仑的汽油 我才不会为它买单
It's gonna get like two miles a gallon. I ain't payin' for all that gas.
作为一个偷车贼你太挑剔了
For a car thief, you are mighty particular.
我可以偷一辆本田
I'll break into the Honda.
我看上去像是会开本田的人？
I look like I'm gonna ride in that Honda to you?
是的
You could.
你可以选一些更经典的车款
And you could pick somethin' with a little more class.
我不想提醒你 但我们准备
I hate to remind you, but we're breakin'
闯进一个固若金汤的海军基地
onto a high-security Navy base.
这不是灰姑娘的舞会
We ain't goin' to the hip-hop opera.
是悲惨世界
It ain't no Les Misérables for you tonight.
悲惨世界
Les Misérables!
伙计 不管怎样
Oh, man, whatever the fuck, man.
别提醒我
Don't remind me.
听着 奎恩斯把钱带回基地不是我的错
Look, it's not my fault Quince took the money back to the base.
我想你说过是你带着钱回基地的
I thought you said you took the money back to the base.
不 我没说过
No, I never said that.
那钱可能在任何地方
So the money could be anywhere.
可能在开曼群岛 可能在天涯海角…
It could be in East Jabip, the Cayman Islands...
不 钱就在基地 好吗？
No, the money is on the base, okay?
我把钱交给了奎恩斯长官
I gave it to Commander Quince at the Camino Real,
他让人带回基地去了
and he told the guys to take it back to the base.
自己则正好准备出去杀你
Right before he took you out and tried to kill you.
那意思他没有说谎
That doesn't mean he's lyin' about the base.
不是每个人都跟你一样偏执 鲍比
Not everybody's as paranoid as you, Bobby. Jeez.
普锐斯怎么样？ 你喜欢普锐斯吗？
What about the Prius? You like the Prius?
卡米诺
Camino Real.
是个旅馆
Yeah, it's a hotel.
我在卡米诺遇见德比的
I met Debbie at the Camino Real.
不是吧
No shit?
- 真的  - 她在那里干活？
- Yeah.  - What was she doin' there?
她说在那等她的男朋友 哈维
She said she was there to meet her boyfriend, Harvey.
等下 你的女朋友有男朋友？
Wait. Your girlfriend has a boyfriend?
她不是我的女朋友
She's not my girlfriend.
妈的
Holy shit.
快选车吧
Yeah, just pick a car.
就这辆
Right here.
你选那一辆？
You picked that one?
是的
Yeah.
你竟然要一辆宾利？
Fuck you want, a fuckin' Bentley?
我来吧
I got it.
恕我无知
Crazy question,
你该不会碰巧认识修雪地摩托的人吧？
you wouldn't have anybody knows how to fix a snowmobile?
未必哦
I don't think so.
你能帮我找下吗？我今晚要用
Would you check for me? I really need it fixed by tonight.
暴风雪要来了？
Why, a big storm coming?
有备无患嘛
You never can be too sure.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
- 你搞什么动作？  - 什么？
- Up with that?  - What?
她对你笑了 你都没有眨眼？
She smiled at you, you didn't wink at her?
我不会对看见的每个女人眨眼
I don't wink at every woman I see.
德州的雪地摩托是吗？ 你一定遇到大问题了 水手
Snowmobile in Texas, huh? You must be in some serious shit, sailor.
你搞了一个新爪子了 哈？
You got yourself a new claw, huh?
- 给我一爪 来碰碰  - 很漂亮
- Gimme claw. Give it a pound.  - It's a beaut.
你还留着我的雨天备用物吗？
You still got my rainy-day stash?
当然啦
Yeah.
稍后再见 史迪格
See ya later, Stig.
没问题
All right.
据说轻声软语的人反而爱使M4步枪 带榴弹炮
You know what they say, talk softly and carry an M-4 with a grenade launcher.
你想要哪把？
Which one you want?
这一把
This one.
你进入基地的计划是什么？
What's your plan for gettin' on the base?
正在想
I'm workin' on it.
记住 一旦我们进入指挥总部
Remember, once we get to the command building,
奎恩斯的办公室在底楼大厅的最后一间
Quince's office is first floor, end of the hall.
如果他不在训练场的话 他每天在那住18小时
If he's not in the field, that's where he lives 18 hours a day.
好的 但你还是没告诉我
Right, right. But you still haven't told me
穿过那扇门的计划是什么
what the plan is to get through the gate.
我有计划 我的意思是 我能想出一个计划
I got a plan. I mean, I'm capable of comin' up with a plan.
我不管你有没有能力
I'm not sayin' you're not capable,
告诉我计划是什么就好
I'm just sayin' you haven't told me. What is it?
还在想
I'm workin' on it.
最好快一些
Better work faster.
再快一些
Much faster.
过来 快点
Move it up. Quickly.
操！
Fuck it.
停下来！
Halt!
他要闯进来！
He's going through!
够快了吗？
That fast enough for ya?
操！
Shit!
上车 快点 无线电联络！
Let's go! Let's go! On the radio now!
返回岗位！
Return to post!
这就是你的计划？
That was your plan?
我们进入海军基地了吧？
Well, we're on the base, aren't we?
这不是一个计划 没有一个正常人会闯入海军基地
That's not a plan. Nobody in their right mind breaks into a naval base.
所以这才是一个聪明绝顶的计划 没人想得到
That's why it's a brilliant plan. No one expected it.
你应该照照镜子 他们被我吓呆了
You shoulda seen your face. Damn, they were surprised.
你别跟着 我来做诱饵
Your stop comin' up. I'll play decoy,
带他们走远一点 试着找到将军 好吗？
lead 'em away, try to get to the Admiral, okay?
好的 出差错的话 我会在船坞等你
All right. Things go wrong, I'll see you back at the boat yard.
不能有差错
Things ain't goin' wrong.
我会得奖章的 我会找到海军上将的 我会得奖章的 看着吧
I'm gettin' a medal. I get to the Admiral, I'm gettin' a medal. Watch.
你会祝我好运吧？
You're gonna wish me luck, aren't ya?
- 说吧伙计 让我听到！ - 祝你好运
- Come on, man, let's hear it!  - Good luck.
奎恩斯的办公室在大厅的尽头
Quince's office at the end of the hall.
记住第一层大厅的尽头！
Remember, first floor, end of the hall!
停下！ 别动！
Halt! Stop where you are!
有人闯入了办公大厅
We have a breach at Status Hall!
上！
Go, go, go, go!
上楼！
Up the stairs!
长官 士官迈克尔・史迪格 编号54033
Sir, Petty Officer Michael Stigman, ID number 540333.
等一下 怎么了？
Wait a minute, what's the problem?
不好意思了 伙计 我也不想这么做的
Shit, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that to you, man.
长官
Sir.
我已服役12年
I've been in service 12 years.
我从没有想过踏入军官食堂 更不要说闯进来了
I've never stepped foot in an officers' mess, much less crashed it.
拜托了 长官 是紧急事件
Please, sir, it's an emergency.
请出去吧
Stand outside, please.
- 让我们谈谈  - 谢谢长官
- Leave us alone.  - Thank you, sir.
我不想那样打你 我道歉
Hey, I'm really sorry about that, man.
我不是有意要打你 我道歉
I didn't mean to hit you like that. I apologize.
我听着呢 水手 坐下吧
I'm listening, sailor. Sit.
谢谢长官
Thank you, sir.
- 再帮我接一次海军上将  - 是 长官
- Try the Admiral again for me.  - Yes, sir.
你相信这些被偷的钱会
And you believed this stolen money
被用来打击贩毒联盟？
would all be used to fight drug cartels?
是 长官 我认为命令是来自上级的有效命令
Yes, sir. I thought the orders came down the valid chain of command.
盲目地忠诚不是忠诚
Blind loyalty is not loyalty.
我知道 长官 所以我在这里
I know that, sir, and that's why I'm here.
好吧 你已经展现出来你有多顽强
Well, you've shown a lot of tenacity
和来这里见我的勇气
and a lot of guts bringing this to me.
谢谢长官 有你这句话就好了
Thank you, sir. That means the world comin' from you.
不幸的是 我什么都帮不了你
Unfortunately, there's nothing I can do for you.
是 长官 我的意思是你只要把基地关闭
Of course, sir. I mean, you can just lock down the base.
你可以逮捕奎恩斯长官
You can arrest Commander Quince.
美国海军不会抢劫银行
The United States Navy does not rob banks.
海军个人也不会抢劫银行
Its personnel did not rob a bank.
我不会让一个犯错的海军人员砧污整个海军正直的形象
I'm not gonna tarnish the integrity of the Navy over one crooked sailor.
如果有从银行里拿来的钱
If there was money taken from the bank
那就是中情局的肮脏基金
that was part of an illegal CIA slush fund,
海军不承认这笔钱的存在
the Navy had no knowledge the fund existed.
六个月的擅离职守？
Your jacket has you six months AWOL?
是 长官
Yes, sir.
会保持原样
It's gonna stay that way.
奎恩斯长官跟你一样 所以他也是擅离职守
Commander Quince's jacket will likewise be amended so he's also AWOL,
这都不是海军的问题
making none of this the Navy's problem.
长官 这样做不对
Sir, this isn't right.
我还有更多办法
Well, I'd offer more,
当手得了坏疽时
but when the hand has gangrene,
你得截肢来保住性命
you chop it off to save the body.
小拇指固然需要 但并非必要
You don't keep the pinkie around just because it meant well.
把史迪格士官扔在大门外
Have Petty Officer Stigman dropped outside the main gate.
他再走近任何一个军事基地
He sets foot on a military base anywhere in the world,
就对他开枪
I want him shot.
扯淡
This is bullshit.
很多像我一样的人为执行命令出生入死
You know, men like me fight and die on the orders of men like you!
没有我们 你肩章的星星不过是该死的装饰品！
Without us, those stars on your shoulder are a fucking costume!
打开保险箱
Open the safe.
你上司知道你在干什么吗？
Does your boss know you're doin' this?
打开
Open it.
也许中情局像已经杀了她 好比杰赛普
Or did the CIA kill her like they did Jessup?
和你有什么关系
What's it to you?
我不喜欢烂摊子
I don't like loose ends.
我也不喜欢
Neither do I...
哈维
Harvey.
我妈叫我哈罗德
Well, my mother named me Harold.
我喜欢哈维这名字 哈维很好听
I like Harvey. Harvey has a nice ring to it.
你不喜欢哈维？
Don't you like Harvey?
- 不知道你说什么  - 不 你知道
- I don't know what you're talkin' about.  - Yes, you do.
最近去过卡米诺皇家酒店？
Been to the Camino Real Hotel lately?
打开保险箱
Open the safe.
清空区域！
Staging area cleared up!
放过来！
Bring it through!
钱在哪儿？
Where's the money?
告诉我德比在哪儿
You tell me where Deb is.
她于此事有染 钱在哪儿？
She's gettin' her nails done. Where is the money?
不知道
I don't know.
把你知道的告诉我
All right, tell me what you do know.
你女朋友找到了中情局在哪儿藏钱
Well, your girl found out where the CIA
就像我做的那样
was stashing the money right about when I did.
我献上一计
And when I told her
建议她和我带着钱跑路 把烂污拆到你和史迪格头上
that she and I could get away with the money by setting you and Stigman up,
她甚至不眨眼就同意了
she didn't even blink.
别对我说谎
Don't lie to me.
鲍比 她不开心吗？
Was she that unhappy, Bobby?
钱在哪儿？ 不要说谎
Where is the money? Don't lie to me.
你和史迪格还活着 你觉得我会傻到把钱在放这吗？
You think I'd keep it here with you and Stigman still alive?
得了 鲍比
Come on, Bobby.
你把钱给她了 是吗？
You gave it to her, didn't you?
是不？
Didn't you?
指挥官 往后退
Commander. Back up.
- 快！ - 六点方向
- Go, go, go, go!  - On your six!
麻利点！
Move, move, move!
全体人员 撤离建筑物
All personnel evacuate the building.
撤回来 在巷子里！
Take the back, in that alley!
到前面去！ 行动！
Go to the front! Let's go!
这边！ 快！
This way! Move!
快点！ 找到他！
Come on, come on! Find him!
安全！
Clear!
你没事吧？
You Okay?
快 我们走
Come on, let's go.
- 还好吗 长官  - 我挺好
You okay, sir? Yeah, I'm fine.
抬水管
Work off the standpipe!
很不错的烤肉
This is really good barbecue.
不尝会后悔的
You don't want to regret not tryin' it.
别浪费时间 直接杀了我吧
Why don't you stop wasting my time and just kill me?
即便鲍比带着钱来
Even if Bobby was coming with the money,
你都会杀我俩的
you'd still kill us both.
但他没来
But he's not coming.
- 他会来  - 不会
- He'll be here.  - No.
他不会的
He won't.
你认为他会让你送死？
You think he's just gonna let you die?
你觉得海军直接到我家找鲍比是巧合吗？
You think it was a coincidence the Navy came looking for Bobby at my house?
如果没有鲍比 我起码能分一半的钱
If I couldn't have Bobby, at least I'd have half of 43 million.
你设计了鲍比・比恩斯
You set up Bobby Beans.
换我也不会为你来送死
I wouldn't be coming for you either.
钱在哪儿？
Where's the money?
拜托 我不知道
Come on. I don't know.
不在这个国家了
Gone, outta the country.
显然也没在海军基地 帕皮
It's certainly not on a Navy base, Papi.
那笔钱在哪里离开你的？
Where does that leave you?
应该说那笔钱会在哪里等我去享受
Exactly where I deserve to be.
- 是我  - 鲍比
- Yeah.  - Bobby.
你迟到了
You're late.
我拿到钱了
I got the money.
我不信
I don't believe you.
我拿到了
No, I got it.
相信我 我会带来给你的
Believe me, I got it. I'll bring it to you.
你在哪儿？
Where are you?
嗨 鲍比
Hi, Bobby.
德比？
Debbie?
他听得到我们吗？
Can he hear us?
挂电话就跑吧
Just hang up the phone and run.
好吧 听我说
Okay, listen to me.
告诉他我拿到钱了
Tell him I got the money.
挂电话
Hang up the phone.
不是你的错 只是…
It's not your fault. Just...
德比
Debbie.
告诉他我拿到钱 好吗？
Tell him I have the money. Okay?
我知道你清楚钱的下落
And I know you know where the money is.
只管告诉他我拿到钱了
Just tell him I have it.
德比 听我说
Debbie, listen to me.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的爱你
I really meant to love you.
德比
Debbie.
你在哪儿？ 德比 你在哪？
Where are you? Debbie, where are you?
你在哪儿？ 德比？
Where are you? Debbie?
喂
Hello?
喂 德比 嗯…
Hello? Debbie? Uh...
等等 我拿到钱了
Wait a minute, I got the money.
他们说什么？ 上将说了什么？
What'd they say? What'd the Admiral say?
上将说了什么？上将说他知道整个事情的经过
What'd the Admiral say? Admiral washed his hands of the whole thing.
海军打发他们上路了
Navy turned their back.
钱在哪儿？
Where's the money?
史迪格 没有钱
There was no money, Stig.
什么？钱不在
What? There was no money.
肯定有钱 我把钱给了奎恩斯
'Course there is. I gave Quince the money.
对 奎恩斯把给了德比 但德比死了
Right, and Quince gave it to Deb, and Deb is dead.
帕皮杀了她
Papi killed her.
操
Fuck him.
我们去墨西哥
Let's go down to Mexico.
把他们打倒 杀光
We'll lure 'em all down, then take every one of 'em out. Kill 'em all.
然后怎样？
And then what?
至少奎恩斯和帕皮会死
Well, at least Quince and Papi'd be dead.
然后又怎样？
And then what?
哦 你让他们逍遥法外吗？
Oh, you just wanna let 'em skate?
史迪格 你没有得到钱吧？
You don't get it, do ya, Stig?
上帝保佑 你还认同规矩吗
I mean, God bless you, you still think there's some kinda code.
没有规矩
There is no code.
你誓死效忠海军 他们当你是炮灰
You followed every order the Navy gave you, they kicked you in the teeth.
没有规矩 史迪格
There is no code, Stig.
没人为了海军拼命 懂吗? 此事与海军无关
No one fights for the Navy, okay? It's not about the Navy.
你是在为你身边的人而战斗
You fight for the guy that's fighting next to you.
这对你没有任何意义吗？
That doesn't mean anything to you?
我要去墨西哥
I'm goin' to Mexico.
你很清楚 我的规矩救了你的命
And just so you know, my code saved your life.
心脏和肩膀之间有三英寸
There's three inches between your heart and your shoulder.
若子弹往左边移三英寸 你就死了
My bullet goes three inches left, you'd be dead.
而我也就不会在这里了
And I wouldn't be here.
奎恩斯杀我是因为我让你活着
'Cause Quince only decided to kill me because I let you live.
你觉得是我失手了？
What, you think I missed, huh?
你觉得是我失手？
Is that what you think? You think I missed?
你几时看我失手过？
When have you ever seen me miss?
你呆着吧 我要去墨西哥
You stay here. I'm goin' to Mexico.
交易还成立吗？
Our deal still stand?
把钱给你 我就可以洗白正身吗？
I give you the money, I walk away clean?
哇 早起的鸟儿有肉吃
Hola. Looks like you had a banner morning.
你最好带了钱来
You better have my money.
都在这里了 一分不少
Right here. Every penny.
鲍比在哪儿？
Where's Bobby?
我们的哲学观有分歧
We had a philosophical fallin' out.
打开你的车子
Open your trunk.
你只需承诺你和朱里奥及所有手下
I just want your word that you and your boys, Ferret Nose Julio, all of 'em,
帮我杀掉奎恩斯
you'll help me kill Commander Quince.
谁是奎恩斯？
Who's Commander Quince?
就是他
That's him.
史迪格先生 你承诺杀掉农场所有人
Mr. Stigman, you promised me $43 million
就给我4300万美元
for killin' everyone on this ranch.
钱都在这儿
Got the money right here, sir.
问题是我也承诺给帕皮同样多的钱
Thing is, I promised Papi the $43 million, too,
恐怕你们要一决高下
so I'm afraid you two are gonna have to duke it out.
或许他和我先杀你 再分钱
Maybe he and I'll just kill you instead and split the money.
帕皮你意下如何？
What do you say, Papi?
4300万美元的一半？
50% of 40 million?
好过百分百死掉吧 对吧？
Better than 100% dead, right?
他会出卖你的 一转身子弹就打穿你的头
He'll double-cross you. Minute your back is turned, bullet in the head.
5 5分成
50-50.
屋顶上的家伙说6 4分成
The guy up on the roof says 60-40.
他浑身上下没有一个地方值得信赖
He ain't got a trustworthy bone in his body.
我回来了　不是吗？
I came back, didn't I?
操蛋的中情局
Fuckin' CIA.
红毛狗 红毛狗(儿歌)
Red rover, red rover.
无论谁拿了我的4300万美元 最好给我出来
Whoever's got my 43.125 million better come the fuck on out.
你也承诺给他钱了？
You offer him the money, too?
我没喊过他
I didn't call him.
在车尾箱里
It's in the trunk!
你为什么告诉他？
Why the fuck did you tell him that?
谢了 指挥官
Thank you, Commander.
史迪格先生 打开车尾箱
Mr. Stigman, come on out and open the trunk.
轻缓优雅点
Nice and slow, now.
看又谁来了？
Well, what do we got here?
听起来像墨西哥婚礼
Sounds like a Mexican wedding.
那是我的1964年雪佛兰吗？
Is that my '64 Impala?
没错
That's correct.
我告诉过你
I told you.
我有熟人
I know a guy.
现在
Now,
谁想见4300万？
who wants to see $43 million?
一瞬间的感觉 你始终让我在追赶自己的尾巴
For a minute there, I thought you had me chasing my tail.
想数数吗？
You want to count it?
如果你骗我 我知道在哪儿能找到你
If you're shortin' me, I know where to find you.
成交吗？
So we're good?
我不是已经给你承诺了嘛
Did I not give you my word?
很好
That's right.
那就不要耍我
Then don't treat me like an asshole.
尽力吧
I'll try my best.
你和史迪格自由了
You and Mr. Stigman are free to go.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
我相信你能找到回家的路
I trust you can find your own way home?
没错
That's right.
－ 鲍比 你在做什么？  - 走吧
- What're you doing, Bobby?  - Let's go.
我不会让他带着钱走的
I'm not gonna let him get away with the money.
走吧 我讨厌这些可恶的家伙
Let's go. I hate these daggone teeth.
他们不会让我们走
They're not just gonna let us go.
- 我有一个B计划  - 嘿 我带着M-16
- I got a plan.  - Hey, I got my M-16.
我带了枪榴弹发射器 还有M-4 我们干一票
I got my grenade launcher, I got my M-4. Let's do this shit.
我有计划 我有能力拿出计划
I got a plan. I'm capable of coming up with a plan.
最好是一个该死的好计划
Well, it better be a goddamn good one.
绝对好计划
It's a good plan.
让暴风雨来得更猛烈些吧
Make it rain.
你的计划就是炸掉4300万吗？
That was your plan? To blow up $43 million?
对 这是个聪明的计划 没人料到
Yeah, that's why it's a brilliant plan. Nobody expected it.
走
Go.
快点搬开
Come on, move it!
该死 搬开
Dumb assholes! Move it!
你来不来？
You comin'?
走 我罩你
Go ahead, I'll be right behind you.
不要失手
Don't miss.
我从不失手
I never miss!
就是说嘛
Told ya.
史迪格！ 史迪格！
Stig! Stig!
不要 不要
Don't do it. Don't do it.
游戏结束
Playtime's over.
别开玩笑
No more fucking around.
现在
Now,
放下武器
drop your weapon.
告诉史迪格先生也放下
Tell Mr. Stigman to do the same.
你自己告诉他
You tell him.
很简单
It's real simple.
要么交易成功 要么死
We can all make a deal or we can all die.
我不做任何交易
I'm not making any deals.
鲍比 告诉你的人
Talk to your man, Bobby.
聪明点
Be the smart one.
你觉得我们只用特雷司・克鲁塞斯银行放钱吗？
You think Tres Cruces is the only stash we got?
我们有20家 到处都有我们的钱
We got 20 more. We got money everywhere.
你改变不了任何现状
You're not gonna change a damn thing.
史迪格？
Stig?
干嘛？
Yeah?
你是我的人 对吗？
You're my people, right?
是的
That's correct.
还好吗？
You good?
从没有这么好过
Never better.
我们不是一种人
We're not people, though.
但却是一家人
This makes us family.
好的 兄弟
All right, brother.
嘿 大兄弟
Hey, se?or Einstein,
你坐在那里的样子看起来逊毙了
you're looking kind of fucked up sittin' there, man.
你还好吗？
You all right?
修剪我的草坪
Mow my lawn.
好吧 你知道什么才酷吗？
Well, you know what was so cool?
坐在1964年产的雪佛兰里
You rolling in on that '64 Impala.
意思是 你看起来很坏
I mean, you looked badass, man.
没错
Yeah, that's right.
听着 还有件事
Listen, one more thing, one more thing.
什么？
What?
把枪给我
Give me your gun.
你在开玩笑吗
You're not serious.
我在开玩笑
Yes, I am.
谢了
Thank you.
经历了这么多你不会要这样做吧？
You're really gonna do this after everything we've been through?
胳膊或腿？
Arm or leg?
这不会让你感觉好点的
This is not gonna make you feel better.
腿吧 因为腿部肌肉多 不会伤到骨头
I'm thinking leg. Because leg, there's more flesh, there's not as much bone.
胳膊就…
The arm will...
你知道你是什么吗？ 你是个十足的…
You know what you are? You are a petty...
贱种
Fucking son of a bitch!
痛吧？ 你真的会杀了我的
Hurts, doesn't it? You know you coulda killed me?
真的吗？ 左边三英寸
Is that right? Three more inches to the left.
不许提
Don't even say it, man.
如此你就不会再和女招待眨眼了
You wouldn't be winking at waitresses anymore.
我不眨眼了 这笔恩怨一笔勾销
I'd still wink, I just wouldn't be able to do anything about it.
你知道我的 我从不失手
You know me, I don't miss.
从不失手 你什么时候看我失手过？
- I never miss.  - When's the last time you saw me miss?
你要把我抬回家
You gonna carry my ass all the way the fuck home.
痛死啦
Oh, shit, man. This burns.
没错
That's correct.
开枪打你的时候我不知道你是谁
You know, I shot you when I didn't know who you were.
之前我们还亲如一家
Before we were family.
没关系
There's a difference.
但现在我们是一家人 我打你是因为我知道你是谁
But we're family now. I shot you because I know who you are.
没道理啊
That ain't right.
他们看起来都一模一样
They definitely got the look.
中情局的都是戴墨镜的笨蛋
Assholes and windshield sunglasses, practically CIA uniform.
伙计们还想要什么吗？
Can I get you boys anything else?
有好吃的甜甜圈吗？
Are your doughnuts any good?
说实话吧 很可怕
Tell you the truth, they're pretty lousy.
听到你那句我们是多么开心
Can't tell you how happy we are to hear that.
注意
You take care.
我看到了
I saw that.
－ 看到什么  - 你眨眼了
- Saw what?  - You winked.
- 这是眼角抽动  - 是的 没错
- That's a twitch.  - Yeah, right.
对于一个 炸毁4300美元的人来说
You know, for a guy who just blew up $43 million,
你太大方了
all of a sudden, you are a very generous tipper.
谁说我炸毁了4300万？
Who said I blew up $43 million?
你说什么呢？
What are you sayin'?
我什么也没说 你听到什么了？
I'm not sayin' anything. What are you hearing?
你话里有话
I'm hearin' somethin'. You're sayin' somethin'.
你若听到 那是因为内心希望听到
Well, if you're hearin' it, it's only because you're hearin' it,
而不是因为我说了什么
not 'cause I'm sayin' it.
你留着多少钱？
How much did you keep?
200万？
Two million?
每人100万
That's like one each.
你现在又想来平分？
So now you get half?
- 我射倒了一半人  - 又怎样？
- Well, I shot half the guys.  - So?
200万？
Two million?